Subscribe
to the bankbajar.com channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com Friends, if you
are in HSBC Bank for an hour, then watch this channel
carefully. In this channel, we will
tell you important information related to ICICI Bank account.
Today, we will tell you that if
you want to make an FD in an ICICI Bank account, then
you do not need to go to the bank.
You can also make it through your mobile application.
For this, the
iMobile application should be activated in your mobile.
If you have not activated this application yet, then
we have
given the link in the description. You can go from there and
activate this application and login.
See, we have logged in to this application
and see at the top here,
your Investment and Secured option is
coming. By clicking here, in it, the
option of Deposit is coming, so
we will click on it and your next page will
open where there is an Open Africa option. By
clicking on it, we will open our account. So,
see, we have clicked here
and your next page will open.  It is where it is
asking for your amount at the top, so
whatever amount of update you want to do it,
you can enter it here, after that it is
asking for your time below, for how long
you want to do it, so by going to this rate,
whatever time you want to give, one
year, two years, six months, whatever you
want to keep, you can fill in the complete details
here, the add is given at the front, for how many
years, for how many months
and for how many days you want to give,
now you can do that here, so if
you want to take the interest on maturity, if you
want to take it monthly, if you
want to take it water, then its option is also
given below, you can go and tick on it,
see we are updating Rs. 10000, it is
important to do it, so we have
cut the amount here and after that
we click on the submit button below, we
submit, see all the details are
visible here, we have done FD for 6 months and one
day and we will
click on the submit button, as soon as we submit,
see our  FD has been created
successfully, here the
maturity amount of our FD is also showing that
how much we will get for Rs.10000 matured amount
and the rate of interest is showing us here, so
friends, in this way you
can still create it from your iMobile application, if friends you liked this video
then like this video and do
subscribe to this channel because
we
take important information related to Quote, so friends, in this way you
can create FD from your account and
along with that there is also an option of your ID here
and you can also take a credit card with FD,
you can add it in updates time
and after this there are many options in it,
so you must subscribe to this channel
so that in the next video
we will tell you how you can open an RD
and
how you can take a credit card with FD, so friends, that's all
for today, we will meet you soon
in the next video, till then thank you
friends, if you also
need any information related to your bank account
or you have any  If you are facing problem
in making FD then you can comment us
or you can mail us, we have
given the mail ID in the description that is
9th Thank you friends